{
    "subject": "resource/The_Greatest_Man_That_Ever_Lived_(Variations_on_a_Shaker_Hymn)",
    "predicate": "ontology/album",
    "object": "resource/Weezer_(2008_album)",
    "human_readable": "The album of 'The Greatest Man That Ever Lived (Variations on a Shaker Hymn)' is Weezer (2008 album)",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9671087861061096,
            "question": "Is 'The Greatest Man That Ever Lived (Variations on a Shaker Hymn)' a studio album?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9641537070274353,
            "question": "What year was the Weezer album 'The Greatest Man That Ever Lived (Variations on a Shaker Hymn)' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9533711671829224,
            "question": "Which band released the album 'The Greatest Man That Ever Lived (Variations on a Shaker Hymn)'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9293873310089111,
            "question": "Are there any notable singles from the album 'The Greatest Man That Ever Lived (Variations on a Shaker Hymn)'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8850532174110413,
            "question": "What is the genre of 'The Greatest Man That Ever Lived (Variations on a Shaker Hymn)'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.813169538974762,
            "question": "What is the title of the Weezer album released in 2008?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5535572171211243,
            "question": "What is unique about the title of this Weezer album?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5479637384414673,
            "question": "Name an album by Weezer."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3712853193283081,
            "question": "Has Weezer won any awards for this album?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.298252671957016,
            "question": "What kind of music does Weezer play?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The album of 'The Greatest Man That Ever Lived (Variations on a Shaker Hymn)' is Weezer (2008 album)",
            "html": "dbpedia_2519_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Weezer won any awards for this album?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2519_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name an album by Weezer.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2519_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is unique about the title of this Weezer album?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2519_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2519_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2519_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2519_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2519_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2519_5.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provide information about the song \"The Greatest Man That Ever Lived (Variations on a Shaker Hymn)\" being part of Weezer's sixth album, which is titled \"Weezer\" and was released in 2008."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}